<resources>
    <string name="app_name">World Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="rk_rj">RK RJ Studio</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="visitors">Visitors Information</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>

    <string name="deccontent_eiffel">
        Gustave Eiffels iconic, wrought-iron 1889 tower, with steps and elevators to observation
        decks.</string>
    <string name="deccontent_taj">
        17th-century, Mughal-style, marble mausoleum with minarets, a mosque
        and famously symmetrical gardens.></string>
    <string name="deccontent_statue">
        Iconic National Monument opened in 1886, offering guided tours, a museum and city views.</string>
    <string name="deccontent_sagrada">
        Antoni Gaudís renowned unfinished church, started in the 1880s, with museum and city views.</string>
    <string name="deccontent_wall">
        Ancient world wonder that winds for more than 5,500 miles across China, with towers and
        walkways.</string>
    <string name="deccontent_colosseum">
        Monumental 3-tiered Roman amphitheater once used for gladiatorial games, with guided tour
        option.</string>

    <string name="taj_time">
        LOCATION"      "-"     "Dharmapuri, Tajganj\n
        CITY"               "-"     "Agra\n
        STATE"            "-"     "Uttar Pradesh\n
        COUNTRY"      "-"     "India\n
        HEIGHT"          "-"     "73 m (240 ft)\n
        BUILT"              "-"     "1632–1653\n
        ARCHITECT"     "-"     "Ahmad Lahauri\n
        ARCH. STYLE"     "-"     "Mughal Arch.\n
        VISITORS"        "-"     "7–8 Million\n
        OPENED"          "-"     "1648\n</string>
    <string name="eiffel_time">
        LOCATION"      "-"     "Champ de Mars\n
        CITY"              "-"        "Paris\n
        COUNTRY"       "-"     "France\n
        HEIGHT"           "-"     "300 m, 324 m to tip\n
        BUILT"              "-"       "1887–89\n
        ARCHITECT"     "-"     "Stephen Sauvestre\n
        VISITORS"        "-"      "7 Million/Year\n
        OPENED"          "-"      "1889\n</string>
    <string name="statue_time">
        LOCATION"     "-"    "Liberty Island\n
        CITY"              "-"      "New York City\n
        COUNTRY"     "-"      "France\n
        HEIGHT"         "-"     "93 meters\n
        BUILT"            "-"     "October 28, 1886\n
        AECHITECT"   "-"     "Frédéric Auguste\n
        VISITORS"     "-"     "4.5 Million/Year\n
        OPENED"       "-"     "1886\n</string>
    <string name="sagrada_time">
        LOCATION"     "-"    "Carrer de Mallorca\n
        CITY"             "-"      "Barcelona\n
        COUNTRY"      "-"      "Spain\n
        HEIGHT"         "-"     "172 m\n
        BUILT"            "-"     "1882-2010\n
        ARCHITECT"   "-"     "Antoni Gaudí\n
        VISITORS"       "-"     "3 Million/Year\n
        OPENED"        "-"     "7 November 2010\n</string>
    <string name="wall_time">
        LOCATION"      "-"    "Huairou\n
        CITY"             "-"      "Beijing\n
        COUNTRY"      "-"     "China\n
        HEIGHT"         "-"     "7.8 m (25 ft 7 in) high\n
        BUILT"             "-"     "2000 years ago\n
        LENGHT"          "-"     "21,196 km\n
        ARCHITECT"    "-"     "Qin Shi Huang\n
        VISITORS"        "-"     "10 Million/Year\n</string>
    <string name="colosseum_time">
        LOCATION"       "-"    "Piazza del Colosseo\n
        CITY"                "-"     "Rome\n
        COUNTRY"        "-"     "Italy\n
        HEIGHT"            "-"     "48 m\n
        ARCHITECT"    "-"     "Vespasian, Titus\n
        BUILT IN"          "-"     "70–80 AD\n
        VISITORS"        "-"     "4 Million/Year\n
        OPENED"          "-"     "80 AD\n</string>

    <string name="visitorinfo_taj">
        ★ OPENING HOURS"   "-"   "Sunrise to Sunset\n\n
        ★ FREE ENTRY"   "-"   "Children below 15 years\n\n
        ★ INDIAN VISITORS"   "-"   "Rs.40\n\n
        ★ SAARC and BIMSTEC COUNTRIES"   "-"   "Rs.530\n\n
        ★ OTHER FOREIGN VISITORS"   "-"   "Rs.1000\n\n
        ★ NOTE"   "-"   "Fridays Closed</string>
    <string name="visitorinfo_eiffel">
        "                        "★ When to visit\n
          ● The Eiffel Tower is open all year!\n\n
        "                        "★ Opening hours\n
          ● From mid-June to early September, 9:00AM to midnight.\n
          ● During the rest of the year, from 9:30AM to 11:00PM.\n\n
        "                        "★ How to get there\n
          ● The two closest métro stops are Bir-Hakeim and Trocadero.\n\n
        "                        "★ ENTRY FEES\n
          ● Under 4 years - Free\n
          ● Aged between 12-24 years - 5€\n
          ● Adults - 10€</string>
    <string name="visitorinfo_statue">
        "                        "★ When to visit\n
          ● Liberty Island is open every day except December 25.\n\n
        "                        "★ Opening hours\n
          ● January 1 to May 26 - 3:30 PM and Grounds close at 4:20 PM\n
          ● May 27 to September 4 - 5:00 PM and Grounds close at 6:20 PM\n
          ● September 5 to October 9 - 4:00 PM and Grounds close at 5:20 PM\n
          ● October 10 to December 31- 3:30 PM and Grounds close at 4:30\n
          ● -" "Christmas Eve, December 24 - 1:30 PM and Grounds close at 2:30 PM\n\n
        "                        "★ How to get there\n
          ● Ferries set off from Battery Park, Brooklyn.\n\n
        "                        "★ ENTRY FEES\n
          ● Under 4 years - Free\n
          ● For 4-12 years - $9\n
          ● Adults (13+) - $18.50\n
          ● Senior (62+) years - $9\n\n
        "                        "★ NOTE\n
          ● There is no extra fee for pedestal access.\n
          ● Crown fee is in addition to the ferry fee.</string>
    <string name="visitorinfo_sagrada">
        "                        "★ When to visit\n
          ● The Sagrada Família is always crowded, but the queues will be at their
        shortest in the early morning or late afternoon\n\n
        "                        "★ Opening hours\n
          ● November to February, 9 am to 6 pm\n
          ● March, 9 am to 7 pm\n
          ● April to September, 9 am to 8 pm\n
          ● October, 9 am to 7 pm\n\n
          ● December(25,26) January(1,6,9)\n\n
        "                        "★ How to get there\n
          ● Take the metro to the Sagrada Familia stop!\n\n
        "                        "★ ENTRY FEES\n
          ● Prices start at 15€\n
          ● Free to see from the outside</string>
    <string name="visitorinfo_wall">
        "                        "★ When to visit\n
          ● All the year!\n
          ● The ideal months for the Great Wall walking and hiking are spring, early
        summer and autumn\n\n
        "                        "★ Opening hours\n
          ● Great Wall of China is open all the Year!\n
          ● All Weekdays ( 07:30 am to 05:30 pm )\n\n
        "                        "★ How to get there\n
          ● The scenic area has two entrances, south entrance and north entrance. One can
        start the visit from either of it.\n
          ➤ Hiking\n
          ➤ Cableway\n
          ➤ Slideway\n\n
        "                        "★ ENTRY FEES\n
          ● Children under 1.2 meters - Free\n
          ● Children between 1.2 and 1.4 meters - CNY 20\n
          ● Adults (13+) - CNY 40\n
          ● Senior (62+) years - CNY 20\n\n
        "                        "★ NOTE\n
          ● If you buy an entrance ticket attached with a postcard of Mutianyu, you need
        to pay CNY 5 more.</string>
    <string name="visitorinfo_colosseum">
        "                        "★ When to visit\n
          ● Open All the Year !\n
          ● Closed 1 January, 1 May and 25 December.\n\n

        "                        "★ Opening hours\n
          ● Last Sunday of October to 15 February:  8.30 - last admission at 15.30 - exit at 16.30 \n\n
          ● 16 February to 15 March:  8.30 - last admission at 16.00 - exit at 17.00\n\n
          ● 16 March to last Saturday of March:  8.30 - last admission at 16.30 - exit at 17.30\n\n
          ● Last Sunday of March to 31 August:  8.30 - last admission at 18.15 - exit at 19.15\n\n
          ● 1 September to 30 September:  8.30 - last admission at 18.00 - exit at 19.00\n\n
          ● 1 October to last Sunday of October:  8.30 - last admission at 17.30 - exit at 18.30 \n\n
        "                  "★ HOW TO REACH THE SITE\n
          ● Roma, Piazza del Colosseo\n
          ● Metro: Line B - Colosseo \n
          ● Bus: Line 75 - 81 - 673 - 175 - 204\n
          ● Tram: Line 3\n\n
        "                        "★ ENTRY FEES\n
          ● Full price - €12\n
          ● Reduced Fee - €7 for European Union citizens\n\n
        "                        "★ NOTE\n
          ● Get there early in the morning to avoid the crowds!\n
          ● Make sure you wear sunscreen, as the Colosseum is open-air.</string>

    <string name="taj_fact_content">
        ● Before his accession to the throne, Shah Jahan was popularly known as Prince Khurram.\n\n
        ● Shah Jahan fell in love with the beautiful Arjumand Bano Begum and married her, making her
        his third wife.\n\n
        ● Shah Jahan lost Mumtaz Mahal, when she died giving birth to their 14h child.\n\n
        ● For the transportation of the construction materials, more than 1,000 elephants were employed.\n\n
        ● As many as 28 different varieties of semi-precious and precious stones were used to adorn
        the Taj with exquisite inlay work.\n\n
        ● Depending on what time of the day it is and whether or not there’s moon at night, Taj Mahal
        appears to be of different color every time. Some even believe that this changing pattern of
        colors depict different moods of a woman.\n\n
        ● Passages from Quran have been used as decorative elements throughout the complex.\n\n
        ● On the sides of the actual tomb of Mumtaz Mahal, 99 names of Allah can be found as calligraphic
        inscriptions.\n\n
        ● Taj Mahal was built in stages, with the plinth and the tomb taking up roughly 15 years.
        Building of minarets, mosque, jawab, and gateway took additional 5 years to be completed.\n\n
        ● Different types of marbles used in construction of Taj Mahal were brought over from many
        different regions and countries: Rajasthan, Punjab, China, Tibet, Afghanistan, Srilanka, and
        Arabia.\n\n
        ● Many precious stones and Lapis Lazuli (a semi-precious stone) were ripped off from its walls
        by the Britishers during the Indian rebellion of 1857.\n\n
        ● Taj Mahal attracts 2-4 million visitors annually with over 200,000 from overseas.\n</string>
    <string name="eiffel_fact_content">
        ● Located on the Champ de Mars in Paris, France, the Eiffel Tower is one of the most well
        known structures in the world.\n\n
        ● The Eiffel Tower was originally built as the entrance arch for the Worlds Fair in 1889.\n\n
        ● It is named after Gustave Eiffel, whose company was in charge of the project.\n\n
        ● The Eiffel Tower is 320 metres (1050 feet) in height and was the tallest man made structure
        in the world for 41 years before being surpassed by the Chrysler Building in New York.\n\n
        ● The Eiffel Tower is made of iron and weighs around 10000 tonnes.\n\n
        ● Around 50 tonnes of paint are added to the Eiffel Tower every 7 years to protect it from
        rust.\n\n
        ● Despite its height, the Eiffel Tower was designed to be wind resistant, swaying only a few
        inches in the wind. It actually moves further when the iron on the sun facing side heats and
        expands, moving the top up to 7 inches (18 centimetres) away from the sun.\n\n
        ● Temperature also alters the height of the Eiffel Tower by up to 6 inches (15 centimetres).\n\n
        ● Millions of people climb the Eiffel Tower every year and it has had over 250 million visitors
        since its opening.\n\n
        ● Visitors can climb up stairs to the first two levels or take a lift which also has access
        to the third and highest level.\n\n
        ● Being so popular, the Eiffel Tower design has been recreated around the world, including
        the half scale replica at the Paris Las Vegas Hotel in Nevada, USA and the full scale Tokyo
        Tower in Japan.\n\n
        ● Not everyone liked the Eiffel Tower when it was first built, with many criticizing its bold
        design.\n\n
        ● The French name for the Eiffel Tower is La Tour Eiffel, it also has the nickname La dame de
        fer which means the iron lady.\n</string>
    <string name="statue_fact_content">
        ● The Statue of Liberty celebrates her birthday on October 28th in honor of the day she was
        officially accepted by the president of the United States in 1886.\n\n
        ● Visitors must climb 354 stairs to reach the Statue of Libertys crown.\n\n
        ● There are 25 windows in Lady Libertys crown.\n\n
        ● The seven spikes on the Statue of Liberty\n crown represent either the seven oceans or the
        seven continents.\n\n
        ● The statue is made of copper and is now green in color because of oxidation from evaporation
        of the seawater surrounding it.\n\n
        ● The Staue of Liberty weighs 450,000 pounds.\n\n
        ● The Statue of Liberty has size 879 sandals that are each 25 feet (7.6m) long.\n</string>
    <string name="sagrada_fact_content">
        ● The ground-breaking for La Sagrada Familia took place in 1882.\n\n
        ● The expected completion date for completion of La Sagrada Familia is 2041.\n\n
        ● The original idea for La Sagrada Familia came from the publisher Josep Bocabella, who was
        inspired after a trip to the Vatican.\n\n
        ● The construction of La Sagrada Familia has been funded by donations.\n\n
        ● After Antoni Gaudis death Domenec Sugranes I Gras took over. His work was interrupted in
        1936 with the Spanish Civil War.\n\n
        ● As of October 2015 La Sagrada Familia is estimated to be 70% complete.\n\n
        ● In 2010 an organ was installed in the un-finished La Sagrada Familia, making it possible
        to hold religious services.\n\n
        ● The Nave, the Crypt, the Museum, the Shop, and the Nativity and Passion towers are accessible
        by tourists.\n\n
        ● The full name of La Sagrada Familia is Basilica I Temple Expiatori de la Sagrada Familia.\n</string>
    <string name="wall_fact_content">
        ● Its main purpose was protection against attacks and invasions from the north.\n\n
        ● The Great Wall of China is the longest structure ever built by humans.\n\n
        ● The widest section of the wall is around 9 metres (30 ft).\n\n
        ● The highest point of the wall is around 8 metres (26 ft)\n\n
        ● The first parts of the wall were built over 2000 years ago.\n\n
        ● A large number of workers have lost their lives while building the wall.\n\n
        ● Earlier sections of the wall were made from stone, wood and compacted earth.\n\n
        ● Some of the well maintained areas of the wall, such as those near Beijing, are popular tourist
        destinations.\n\n
        ● While some parts of the wall have been preserved or renovated, other parts have been vandalised
        or destroyed to make way for construction.\n\n
        ● Rumours that astronauts can see the Great Wall of China from the Moon with the naked eye
        are untrue.\n</string>
    <string name="colosseum_fact_content">
        ● Construction began in 72 AD under the emperor Vespasian.\n\n
        ● It took 60,000 Jewish slaves to build the Colosseum. It was built of stone and concrete.\n\n
        ● There were also re-enactments of famous battles and executions held in the amphitheatre.\n\n
        ● Some of the events and games that were held in the Colosseum lasted for up to 100 days.\n\n
        ● They Romans had the earliest form of a Skydome. If it rained they stretched a red canvas
        over the entire Colosseum.\n\n
        ● After the Colosseum was partially destroyed by the earthquake, some of the fallen pieces
        were used to build St Peters Basilica.\n\n
        ● It is one of the most popular Roman tourist attractions today.\n\n
        ● Ray Charles, Paul McCartney, Billy Joel and Elton John have all performed concerts at the
        Colloseum.\n\n
        ● The Colosseum has become a symbol against capital punishment. The death penalty was abolished
        in Italy in 1948.\n</string>

    <string name="about_taj_1">
        ★ The Taj Mahal is an ivory-white marble mausoleum on the south bank of the Yamuna river in
        the Indian city of Agra. The Taj Mahal was commissioned by Shah Jahan in 1631, to be built
        in the memory of his wife Mumtaz Mahal, a Persian princess who died giving birth to their
        14th child, Gauhara Begum.\n </string>
    <string name="about_taj_2">
        ★ The tomb is the centrepiece of a 17-hectare complex, which includes a mosque and a guest
        house, and is set in formal gardens bounded on three sides bya crenellated wall.\n\n
        ★ The Taj Mahal complex is believed to have been completed in its entirety in 1653 at a cost
        estimated at the time to be around 32 million rupees, which in 2015 would be approximately
        52.8 billion rupees (U.S. $827 million).\n\n
        ★ The construction project employed some 20,000 artisans under the guidance of a board of
        architects led by the court architect to the emperor, Ustad Ahmad Lahauri.\n\n
        ★ Described by Nobel laureate Rabindranath Tagore as THE TEAR-DROP ON THE CHEEK OF TIME ,
        it is regarded by many as the best example of Mughal architecture and a symbol of Indias rich
        history. </string>
    <string name="about_eiffel_1">
        ★ The Eiffel Tower is a wrought iron lattice tower on the Champ de Mars in Paris, France. It
        is named after the engineer Gustave Eiffel, whose company designed and built the tower.\n\n
        ★ Constructed from 1887–89, it was initially criticizedby some of Frances leading artists
        for its design, but it has become a globalcultural icon ofFrance and one of the most recognisable
        structures in the world. The Eiffel Tower is the most-visited paid monument in the world;
        6.91 million people ascended it in 2015.\n\n
        ★ The Eiffel Tower by Gustave Eiffel.\n</string>
    <string name="about_eiffel_2">
        ★ The tower is 324 metres (1,063 ft) tall, about the same height as an 81-storey building,
        and the tallest structure in Paris. Its base is square, measuring 125 metres (410 ft) on each
        side.\n\n
        ★ The tower has three levels for visitors, with restaurants on the first and second levels.
        The top levels upper platform is 276 m (906 ft) above the ground – the highest observation
        deck accessible to the public in the European Union. \n\n
        ★ The main structural work was completed at the end of March 1889 and, on 31 March, Eiffel
        celebrated by leading a group of government officials, accompanied by representatives of the
        press, to the top of the tower. Because the lifts were not yet in operation, the ascent
        was made by foot, and took over an hour, with Eiffel stopping frequently to explain various
        features.\n\n
        ★ Eiffel had a permit for the tower to stand for 20 years. It was to be dismantled in 1909,
        when its ownership would revert to the City of Paris. The City had planned to tear it down
        but as the tower proved to be valuable for communication purposes, it was allowed to remain
        after the expiry of the permit.</string>
    <string name="about_statue_1">
        ★ The Statue of Liberty is a colossal neoclassical sculpture on Liberty Island in New
        York Harbor in New York City, in the United States. The copper statue, a gift from the people
        of France to the people of the United States\n\n
        ★ The Statue of Liberty is a figure of a robed woman representing Libertas, a Roman
        liberty goddess - also incorporating some elements reminiscent of another Roman deity, Sol
        Invictus. She holds a torch above her head with her right hand, and in her left hand carries
        a tabula ansata inscribed in Roman numerals with JULY IV MDCCLXXVI (July 4, 1776), the date
        of the U.S. Declaration of Independence. A broken chain lies at her feet. The statue became
        an icon of freedom and of the United States, and was a welcoming sight to immigrants arriving
        from abroad.\n\n
        ★ The statue was administered by the United States Lighthouse Board until 1901 and then
        by the Department of War; since 1933 it has been maintained by the National Park Service.
        Public access to the balcony around the torch has been barred for safety since 1916.\n\n
        ★ The Liberty of Statue by French sculptor Frédéric Auguste Bartholdi and built by Gustave
        Eiffel.\n</string>
    <string name="about_statue_2">
        ★ Bartholdi and Laboulaye considered how best to express the idea of American liberty. In
        early American history, two female figures were frequently used as cultural symbols of the
        nation. \n\n
        ★ One of these symbols, the personified Columbia, was seen as an embodiment of the
        United States in the manner that Britannia was identified with the United Kingdom and Marianne
        came to represent France. Columbia had supplanted the earlier figure of an Indian princess,
        which had come to be regarded as uncivilized and derogatory toward Americans.\n\n
        ★ Fundraising for the statue had begun in 1882. The committee organized a large number of
        money-raising events. As part of one such effort, an auction of art and manuscripts, poet
        Emma Lazarus was asked to donate an original work. She initially declined, stating she could
        not write a poem about a statue. \n\n
        ★ On June 17, 1885, the French steamer Isère, laden with the Statue of Liberty, reached the
        New York port safely. After 5 months of daily calls to donate to the statue fund, on August
        11, 1885,the World announcedthat $102,000 had been raised from 120,000 donors, and that 80
        percent of the total had been received in sums of less than one dollar.\n\n
        ★ A ceremony of dedication was held on the afternoon of October 28, 1886. President Grover
        Cleveland, the former New York governor, presided over the event.[100] On the morning of the
        dedication, a parade was held in New York City; estimates of the number of people who watched
        it ranged from several hundred thousand to a million.</string>
    <string name="about_sagrada_1">
        ★ The Basílica i Temple Expiatori de la Sagrada Família (Basilica and Expiatory Church
        of the Holy Family) is the largest unfinished Roman Catholic church in world and is located
        in Barcelona, designed by Catalan architect Antoni Gaudí (1852–1926). Gaudís work on the
        building is part of a UNESCO World Heritage Site.\n\n
        ★ In 1882, construction of Sagrada Família started under architect Francisco Paula de
        Villar. In 1883, when Villar resigned, Gaudí took over as chief architect, transforming the
        project with his architectural and engineering style, combining Gothic and curvilinear Art
        Nouveau forms. Gaudí devoted the remainder of his life to the project, and at the time of his
        death at age 73 in 1926, less than a quarter of the project was complete.\n\n
        ★ The basilica has a long history of dividing the citizens of Barcelona: over the initial
        possibility it might compete with Barcelonas cathedral, over Gaudís design itself, over the
        possibility that work after Gaudís death disregarded his design,and the 2007 proposal to
        build an underground tunnel of Spains high-speed rail link to France which could disturb its
        stability.\n\n
        ★ Describing Sagrada Família, art critic Rainer Zerbst said it is probably impossible
        to find a church building anything like it in the entire history of art, and Paul Goldberger
        describes it as the most extraordinary personal interpretation of Gothicarchitecture since
        the Middle Ages.</string>
    <string name="about_sagrada_inside">
        ★ The Basilica of the Sagrada Família was the inspiration of a bookseller, Josep Maria
        Bocabella, founder of Asociación Espiritual de Devotos de San José\n </string>
    <string name="about_sagrada_2">
        ★ On the subject of the extremely long construction period, Gaudí is said to have remarked:
        My client is not in a hurry. When Gaudí died in 1926, the basilica was between 15 and 25
        percent complete. After Gaudís death, work continued under the direction of Domènec Sugrañes
        i Gras until interrupted by the Spanish Civil War in 1936.\n\n
        ★ Parts of the unfinished basilica and Gaudís models and workshop were destroyed during the
        war by Catalan anarchists. The present design is based on reconstructed versions of the plans
        that were burned in a fire as well as on modern adaptations. Since 1940 the architects Francesc
        Quintana, Isidre Puig Boada, Lluís Bonet i Gari and Francesc Cardoner have carried on the work.
        The illumination was designed by Carles Buïgas. \n\n
        ★ Parts of the unfinished basilica and Gaudís models and workshop were destroyed during
        the war by Catalan anarchists. The present design is based on reconstructed versions of the
        plans that were burned in a fire as well as on modern adaptations. Since 1940 the architects
        Francesc Quintana, Isidre Puig Boada, Lluís Bonet i Gari and Francesc Cardoner have carried
        on the work. The illumination was designed by Carles Buïgas.\n\n
        ★ The style of la Sagrada Família is variously likened to Spanish Late Gothic, Catalan
        Modernism and to Art Nouveau or Catalan Noucentisme. While the Sagrada Família falls within
        the Art Nouveau period, Nikolaus Pevsner points out that, along with Charles Rennie Macintosh
        in Glasgow, Gaudí carried the Art Nouveau style far beyond its usual application as a surface
        decoration.</string>
    <string name="about_sagrada_architects">★ The Sagrada Familia by Antoni Gaudí.\n</string>
    <string name="about_wall_1">
        ★ The Great Wall of China is a series of fortifications made of stone, brick, tamped
        earth, wood, and other materials, generally built along an east-to-west line across the
        historical northern borders of China to protect the Chinese states and empires against the
        raids and invasions of the various nomadic groups of the Eurasian Steppe. Several walls were
        being built as early as the 7th century BC; these, later joined together and made bigger and
        stronger, are collectively referred to as the Great Wall.\n\n
        ★ Especially famous is the wall built in 220–206 BC by Qin Shi Huang, the first Emperor
        of China. Little of that wall remains. The Great Wall has been rebuilt, maintained, and
        enhanced over various dynasties; the majority of the existing wall is from the Ming Dynasty
        (1368–1644).\n\n
        ★ Apart from defense, other purposes of the Great Wall have included border controls,
        allowing the imposition of duties on goods transported along the Silk Road, regulation or
        encouragement of trade and the control of immigration and emigration. Furthermore, the
        defensive characteristics of the Great Wall were enhanced by the construction of watch towers,
        troop barracks, garrison stations\n\n
        ★ The Great Wall of China by Qin Shi Huang, to protect dynasty\n</string>
    <string name="about_wall_2">
        ★ The Chinese were already familiar with the techniques of wall-building by the time of the
        Spring and Autumn period between the 8th and 5th centuries BC. During this time and the
        subsequent Warring States period, the states of Qin, Wei, Zhao, Qi, Yan, and Zhongshan all
        constructed extensive fortifications to defend their own borders. Built to withstand the
        attack of small arms such as swords and spears, these walls were made mostly by stamping
        earth and gravel between board frames.\n\n
        ★ The Great Wall concept was revived again under the Ming in the 14th century, and following
        the Ming armys defeat by the Oirats in the Battle of Tumu. The Ming had failed to gain a clear
        upper hand over the Mongolian tribes after successive battles, and the long-drawn conflict was
        taking a toll on the empire. The Ming adopted a new strategy to keep the nomadic tribes out
        by constructing walls along the northern border of China. \n\n
        ★ When China opened its borders to foreign merchants and visitors after its defeat in the
        First and Second Opium Wars, the Great Wall became a main attraction for tourists. The
        travelogues of the later 19th century further enhanced the reputation and the mythology of
        the Great Wall, such that in the 20th century, a persistent misconception exists about the
        Great Wall of China being visible from the Moon or even Mars.\n\n
        ★ While portions north of Beijing and near tourist centers have been preserved and even
        extensively renovated, in many other locations the Wall is in disrepair. Those parts might
        serve as a village playground or a source of stones to rebuild houses and roads.</string>
    <string name="about_colosseum_1">
        ★ The Colosseum or Coliseum , also known as the Flavian Amphitheatre, is an oval
        amphitheatre in the centre of the city of Rome, Italy. Built of travertine, tuff, and brick-
        faced concrete, it is the largest amphitheatre ever built. \n\n
        ★ The Colosseum is situated just east of the Roman Forum. Construction began under the
        emperor Vespasian in AD 72,[2] and was completed in AD 80 under his successor and heir Titus.
        Further modifications were made during the reign of Domitian (81–96). These three emperors are
        known as the Flavian dynasty, and the amphitheatre was named in Latin for its association with
        their family name (Flavius).\n\n
        ★ The Colosseum could hold, it is estimated, between 50,000 and 80,000 spectators,
        having an average audience of some 65,000; it was used for gladiatorial contests and public
        spectacles such as mock sea battles, animal hunts, executions, re-enactments of famous battles,
        and dramas based on Classical mythology.\n\n
        ★ The name Colosseum has long been believed to be derived from a colossal statue of Nero
        nearby. This statue was later remodeled by Neros successors into the likeness of Helios or
        Apollo, the sun god, by adding the appropriate solar crown.\n\n
        ★ In the 8th century, a famous epigram attributed to the Venerable Bede celebrated the
        symbolic significance of the statue in a prophecy that is variously quoted: Quamdiu stat
        Colisæus,stat et Roma; quando cadet colisæus, cadet et Roma; quando cadet Roma, cadet et
        mundus. This isoften mistranslated to refer to the Colosseum rather than the Colossus\n\n
        ★ Vespasian and Titus, builders of the Colosseum\n</string>
    <string name="about_colosseum_2">
        ★ The site chosen was a flat area on the floor of a low valley between the Caelian, Esquiline
        and Palatine Hills, through which a canalised stream ran. By the 2nd century BC the area was
        densely inhabited. It was devastated by the Great Fire of Rome in AD 64, following which Nero
        seized much of the area to add to his personal domain. \n\n
        ★ He built the grandiose Domus Aurea on the site, in front of which he created an artificial
        lake surrounded by pavilions, gardens and porticoes. The existing Aqua Claudia aqueduct was
        extended to supply water to the area and the gigantic bronze Colossus of Nero was set up
        nearby at the entrance to the Domus Aurea.\n\n
        ★ The Colosseum underwent several radical changes of use during the medieval period. By the
        late 6th century a small chapel had been built into the structure of the amphitheater, though
        this apparently did not confer any particular religious significance on the building as a
        whole. The arena was converted into a cemetery.\n\n
        ★ The numerous vaulted spaces in the arcades under the seating were converted into housing and
        workshops, and are recorded as still being rented out as late as the 12th century. Around
        1200 the Frangipani family took over the Colosseum and fortified it, apparently using it as
        a castle.\n\n
        ★ During the 16th and 17th century, Church officials sought a productive role for the Colosseum.
        Pope Sixtus V (1585–1590) planned to turn the building into a wool factory to provide employment
        for Romes prostitutes, though this proposal fell through with his premature death. In 1671
        Cardinal Altieri authorized its use for bullfights; a public outcry caused the idea to be hastily
        abandoned.\n\n
        ★ The arena itself was 83 meters by 48 meters. It comprised a wooden floor covered by sand,
        covering an elaborate underground structure called the hypogeum . The hypogeum was not part
        of the original construction but was ordered to be built by Emperor Domitian.\n</string>

    <string name="contactinfo_taj">
        ★ Official Contacts\n
          "       "" "+91 05622226434\n
          "       "" "( 10:00 am to 5:00 pm )\n\n
        ★ info@tajmahal.gov.in\n
          "       "" "( excluding declared holidays and sundays )\n\n
        ★ Tourist Police Station\n
          "       "" "+91 9454402765\n\n
        ★ Tourist Helpline\n
          "       "" "+91 9356462115\n
          "       "" "( 06:30 am to 5:30 pm )\n\n</string>
    <string name="contactinfo_eiffel">
        ★ Official Contacts\n
          "       "" "+33 892 70 10 39\n
          "       "" "( 09:30 am to 12:00 am )\n\n
        ★ info@eiffeltower.gov.in\n
          "       "" "( excluding declared holidays and sundays )\n</string>
    <string name="contactinfo_statue">
        ★ Official Contacts\n
          "       "" "(646) 356-2403\n
          "       "" "(Answered Weekdays 09:00 am to 04:00 pm )\n\n
        ★ info@libertyisland.gov.in\n
          "       "" "( excluding declared holidays and sundays )\n</string>
    <string name="contactinfo_sagrada">
        ★ Official Contacts\n
          "       "" "(+34) 932 080 414\n
          "       "" "(From Monday to Thursday from 8:00 AM to 5:45 PM.)\n\n
          "       "" "(Friday from 8:00 AM to 2:30 PM.)\n\n
        ★ info@sagradafamilia.gov.in\n
          "       "" "( excluding declared holidays and sundays )\n\n</string>
    <string name="contactinfo_wall">
        ★ Official Contacts\n
          "       "" "(646) 356-2403\n
          "       "" "(Answered Weekdays 09:00 am to 04:00 pm )\n\n
        ★ info@libertyisland.gov.in\n
          "       "" "( excluding declared holidays and sundays )\n</string>
    <string name="contactinfo_colosseum">
        ★ Official Contacts\n
          "       "" "+39 06 3996 7700\n
          "       "" "(Answered Weekdays 09:00 am to 04:00 pm )\n\n
        ★ ssba-rm.colosseo@beniculturali.it\n
          "       "" "( excluding declared holidays and sundays )\n\n</string>

    <string name="sagrada_in">Interior</string>
    <string name="sagrada_interior1">
        ★ The church plan is that of a Latin cross with five aisles. The central nave vaults reach
        forty-five metres (150 ft) while the side nave vaults reach thirty metres (100 ft). The
        transept has three aisles. The columns are on a 7.5 metre (25 ft) grid.\n</string>
    <string name="sagrada_interior2">
        ★ The crossing rests on the four central columns of porphyry supporting a great hyperboloid
        surrounded by two rings of twelve hyperboloids (currently under construction). The central
        vault reaches sixty metres (200 ft). The apse is capped by a hyperboloid vault reaching
        seventy-five metres (250 ft).\n</string>
    <string name="sagrada_interior3">
        ★ The columns of the interior are a unique Gaudí design. Besides branching to support their
        load, their ever-changing surfaces are the result of the intersection of various geometric
        forms. The simplest example is that of a square base evolving into an octagon as the column
        rises, then a sixteen-sided form, and eventually to a circle.\n</string>
    <string name="from_the_moon_1">
        ★ One of the earliest known references to the myth that the Great Wall can be seen from the
        moon appears in a letter written in 1754 by the English antiquary William Stukeley. Stukeley
        wrote that, This mighty wall of four score miles [130 km] in length is only exceeded by the
        Chinese Wall, which makes a considerable figure upon the terrestrial globe, and may be
        discerned at the Moon.</string>
    <string name="from_the_moon_2">
        ★ The claim the Great Wall is visible from the moon has been debunked many times, but is still
        ingrained in popular culture. The wall is a maximum 9.1 m (29 ft 10 in) wide, and is about the
        same color as the soil surrounding it. Based on the optics of resolving power (distance versus
        the width of the iris: a few millimeters for the human eye, meters for large telescopes) only
        an object of reasonable contrast to its surroundings which is 110 km (70 mi) or more in diameter
        (1 arc-minute) would be visible to the unaided eye from the Moon, whose average distance from
        Earth is 384,393 km (238,851 mi).</string>
    <string name="how_was_built">
        ★ The majestic Great Wall was built with wisdom, dedication, blood, sweat, and tears. Families
        were separated, and many workers died and were interred as part of the Great Wall itself.\n\n
        ➤ Workers : soldiers, peasants, rebels\n
        ➤ Materials: stone, soil, sand, brick\n
        ➤ Material delivery: by hand, rope, cart, goat</string>
    <string name="how_built">How Wall is Built</string>
    <string name="Wall_from_the_moon">Wall from the Moon</string>
    <string name="contactname">Helpline</string>
    <string name="communicate">Communicate</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="item_about">About</string>
    <string name="update_content">This Content Will Be Shown in Next Update</string>
    <string name="dialogue">
        WORLD TOUR GUIDE application briefs about the various Tourism locations in the world.
        Selected countries with 4 different locations are available in the Application. If you
        like this App , share this with yours friends.\n\n
        ★ ★ ★ ★ THANK YOU ★ ★ ★ ★

    </string>
    <string name="geo_format">geo:%f,%f</string>
    <string name="title_wall">Great Wall of China</string>
    <string name="title_potala">Potala Palace</string>
    <string name="title_terracotta">Terracotta Army</string>
    <string name="title_forbidden">Forbidden City</string>
    <string name="sub_title_wall">Huairou, China</string>
    <string name="sub_title_potala">Lhasa , Tibet</string>
    <string name="sub_title_terracotta">Xi\'an , Shaanxi</string>
    <string name="sub_title_forbidden">Dongcheng , Beijing</string>
    <string name="title_eiffel">Eiffel Tower</string>
    <string name="title_disney">Disney Land</string>
    <string name="title_cannes">Cannes</string>
    <string name="title_louvre">The Louvre</string>
    <string name="title_taj">Taj Mahal</string>
    <string name="title_hill">Hill Stations</string>
    <string name="title_falls">Dudhsagar Falls</string>
    <string name="ghats">Ghats</string>
    <string name="title_colosseum">Colosseum</string>
    <string name="title_leaning">Leaning Tower of Pisa</string>
    <string name="title_amalfi">Amalfi Coast</string>
    <string name="title_piazza">Piazza San Marco</string>
    <string name="title_sagrada">Sagrada Família</string>
    <string name="majorka">Majorca</string>
    <string name="alhambra">Alhambra</string>
    <string name="ibiza">Ibiza</string>
    <string name="title_statue">Statue of Liberty</string>
    <string name="title_canyon">Grand Canyon</string>
    <string name="title_yosemite">Yosemite National Park</string>
    <string name="title_rushmore">Mount Rushmore National Memorial</string>
    <string name="sub_title_eiffel">5 Avenue Anatole France , Paris</string>
    <string name="sub_title_disney">Marne-la-Vallée , Paris</string>
    <string name="sub_title_cannes">French Riviera , France</string>
    <string name="sub_title_louvre">Rue de Rivoli , Paris</string>
    <string name="sub_title_taj">Agra , Uttar Pradeh</string>
    <string name="sub_title_hill">Munnar , Kerala</string>
    <string name="sub_title_falls">Goa , Panjim</string>
    <string name="sub_title_ghats">Varanasi , Uttar Pradesh</string>
    <string name="sub_title_colosseum">Piazza del Colosseo , Rome</string>
    <string name="sub_title_leaning">Piazza del Duomo , Pisa</string>
    <string name="sub_title_amalfi">Amalfi Province of Salerno , Italy</string>
    <string name="sub_title_piazza">Venezia VE , Italy</string>
    <string name="sub_title_sagrada">Carrer de Mallorca , Barcelona</string>
    <string name="sub_title_majorka">Island in Spain</string>
    <string name="sub_title_alhambra">Granada , Spain</string>
    <string name="sub_title_ibiza">Island in the Mediterranean Sea</string>
    <string name="sub_title_statue">New York Harbor , New York City</string>
    <string name="sub_title_canyon">Colorado River , Arizona</string>
    <string name="sub_title_yosemite">California , U.S.A</string>
    <string name="sub_title_rushmore">Keystone , South Dakota</string>
    <string name="check_out_app">Check out App</string>
    <string name="tex_plain">text/plain</string>
    <string name="card_text_india">India</string>
    <string name="card_text_italy">Italy</string>
    <string name="card_text_china">China</string>
    <string name="card_text_usa">U.S.A</string>
    <string name="card_text_spain">Spain</string>
    <string name="card_text_france">France</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="ranks">Ranks #</string>
    <string name="world">" "in World</string>

</resources>
